<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<floater can_close="true" can_drag_on_left="false" can_minimize="true"
     can_resize="false" height="440" min_height="100" min_width="100"
     name="floater_about" rect_control="FloaterAboutRect"
     title="About grid viewer" width="470">
  <tab_container
		 follows="all"
		 bottom="10"
		 left="10"
		 height="405"
		 width="450"
		 name="about_tab"
		 tab_position="top">
    <panel
      border="true"
      height="386"
      label="Version"
      help_topic="about_support_tab"
      name="support_panel">
      <text_editor bottom="28" embedded_items="false"
         follows="left|top|right|bottom" font="SansSerif" height="352" left="6"
         max_length="65536" mouse_opaque="true" name="support_editor" width="423"
         word_wrap="true" />
      <button follows="left|top" label="Copy to Clipboard" name="copy_btn"
         left="5" bottom="0" top_pad="5" height="20" width="180" />
    </panel>
    <panel
        border="true"
        label="Credits"
        height="386"
        help_topic="about_credits_tab"
        name="credits_panel">

	<text_editor bottom="6" embedded_items="false"
	     follows="left|top|right|bottom" font="SansSerifSmall" height="374" left="6"
  max_length="65536" mouse_opaque="true" name="credits_editor" width="423"
  word_wrap="true">
  This meta-impy viewer is based on the Imprudence viewer, and brought to you by Dave and Chris.
  
  http://onefang.net/redmine/ for bug reports, feature requests, bitching, and downloads.
  http://github.com/onefang/meta-impy for the source code.

  The Imprudence Viewer was rocked hard by:
  Jacek Antonelli, McCabe Maxsted, Armin Weatherwax, Elektra Hesse, and CodeBastard Redgrave.

  http://kokuaviewer.org/

  Imprudence is so awesome thanks to contributions from many generous people:

  For their patches and code contributions, we thank Admiral Admiral, Aimee Trescothick, Aleric Inglewood, Alissa Sabre, Archimedies Plutonian, Angus Boyd, Ansariel Hiller, Ardy Lay, Asuka Neely, Balp Allen, Carjay McGinnis, Chalice Yao, Dale Glass, Damian Delacrois, Danny Nolan, Felix Duesenburg, Geneko Nemeth, Henri Beauchamp, Katharine Berry, KirstenLee Cinquetti, Kitty Barnett, Latif Khalifa, Lilly Zenovka, Makomk Makosen, Mana Janus, Matthew Dowd, Michelle2 Zenovka, Mm Alder, Nemurimasu Neiro, Nicholaz Beresford, Patrick Sapinski, Paul Churchill, Peter Lameth, Robin Cornelius, Stephen Zenith, Thickbrick Sleaford, Thomas Shikami, Tom Meta, tx Oh, Vaalith Jinn, Vadim Bigbear, Vex Streeter, Zi Ree, and Zwagoth Klaar.

  For their WindLight presets, we thank Ana Lutetia, CodeBastard Redgrave, and Torley Linden.
  
  Thanks also to the developer(s) of the Emerald Viewer, Hippo Viewer, Cool VL Viewer, Snowglobe Viewer, meta 7 Viewer, FrozenGlobe Viewer, and Meerkat Viewer for viewer enhancements we have incorporated, as well as Kitty Barnett for RLVa. Special thanks to the folks at Linden Lab for releasing the viewer source, without which this endeavor would have been impossible.
  
  For a complete list of who did what, read the release notes!

  Many thanks to the many residents in many grids who contributed towards this viewer in countless ways.

        3Dconnexion SDK Copyright © 1992-2007 3Dconnexion
        APR Copyright © 2000-2004 The Apache Software Foundation
        cURL Copyright © 1996-2002, Daniel Stenberg, (daniel@haxx.se)
        DBus/dbus-glib Copyright © 2002, 2003  CodeFactory AB / Copyright © 2003, 2004 Red Hat, Inc.
        expat Copyright © 1998, 1999, 2000 Thai Open Source Software Center Ltd.
        FreeType Copyright © 1996-2002, The FreeType Project (www.freetype.org).
        GL Copyright © 1999-2004 Brian Paul.
        Havok.com(TM) Copyright © 1999-2001, Telekinesys Research Limited.
        jpeg2000 Copyright © 2001, David Taubman, The University of New South Wales (UNSW)
        jpeglib Copyright © 1991-1998, Thomas G. Lane.
        ogg/vorbis Copyright © 2001, Xiphophorus
        OpenSSL Copyright © 1998-2002 The OpenSSL Project.
        SDL Copyright © 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002 Sam Lantinga
        SSLeay Copyright © 1995-1998 Eric Young (eay@cryptsoft.com)
        xmlrpc-epi Copyright © 2000 Epinions, Inc.
        zlib Copyright © 1995-2002 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler.
        google-perftools Copyright © 2005, Google Inc.
        Code from FAAD2 is copyright © Nero AG, www.nero.com

        All rights reserved.  See LICENSE-libraries.txt for details.

        Voice chat Audio coding: Polycom(R) Siren14(TM) (ITU-T Rec. G.722.1 Annex C)


  I live in the future, just waiting for the rest of you to catch up. -- onefang Rejected
      </text_editor>
    </panel>
  </tab_container>
  <string name="you_are_at">
		You are at [POSITION]
	</string>
</floater>

